Resume

# Arun Siddappaji

DOWNLOAD CV

arunsisu@gmail.com

## **Experience Summary**

**20+ Years** Experience in Software Testing. 10+ Years Management Experience. Excellent skills in Building and Mentoring Engineering team in Storage Domain. Successfully managed large complex enterprise Software Releases for quality in collaboration with direct and team across the globe. Excellent interpersonal skills working with Program management, product management, Development team, Architects, Operations to develop and execute project and organizational strategies. Experience in building talented engineering teams including Managers, Leads and Senior Individual contributors. Experience in managing talented team working across technologies – SAS, RAID, SAN, File Systems, Storage Management, Server Technologies, Operating System Internals & Virtualization. Successfully managed team delivering end-to-end solutions in Storage products. Person with passion on People Management and Mentoring.

# **Experience**

Company	Peak Position	Period
	Senior Manager - Test Engineering	May 2011 to Jun 2018 (6+Years)

#### **Expertise Demonstrated:**

Project Management, People Management, Customer Engagement, Budget Management, Contineous Efficiency Drives, Cross-Geo Management.

Company	Peak Position	Period
<b>vm</b> ware <sup>®</sup>	Project Manager - Test Engineering	Jun 2008 to May 2011 (3+ Years)

#### **Expertise Demonstrated:**

Project Management, People Management, Budget Management, Contineous Efficiency Drives, Cross-Geo Management.

Company	Peak Position	Period
(intel®	Project Lead	Oct 2005 to Jun 2008 (~3 Years)

### **Expertise Demonstrated:**

Project Schedules, Risk Assessment, Project Reports, Quality Management, Contineous Team Efficiency Drives, Cross-Geo Interactions

Company	Peak Position	Period
sasken Make the Right Connection	Technical Lead	July 2005 to Oct 2005 (~2.5 Years)

### **Expertise Demonstrated:**

Project Deliveries, Schedule Management, Risk Alarams, Project Reports

Company	Peak Position	Period
HEWLETT® PACKARD	Senior Engineer	Feb 2000 to Oct 2003 (~4Years)

### **Expertise Demonstrated:**

Project Deliveries, Schedule Management, Risk Alarams, Project Reports

# **Education**

Qualification	Institute/School	Year
Bachelor Of Engineering	Sri Jaya Chamarajendra College of	1994
(Electronics &	Engineering, Mysore University,	-
Communication)	Mysore	1998

Follow me:

email github.com/arunsiddappaji